{
  "1": {
    "1": {
      "question": "4+5",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    "2": {
      "question": "2*4",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    "3": {
      "question": "8-3",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    "4": {
      "question": "3+8",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    "5": {
      "question": "12-6",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    "6": {
      "question": "9*7",
      "answer": "63"
    },
    "7": {
      "question": "5-4",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    "8": {
      "question": "6*4",
      "answer": "24"
    }
  },
  "2": {
    "1": {
      "question": "3*9",
      "answer": "21"
    },
    "2": {
      "question": "11-7",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    "3": {
      "question": "4+3",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    "4": {
      "question": "6+8",
      "answer": "14"
    }
  }
}